<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Beautiful Brasov</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="text_login">Login</string>
    <string name="text_register">Register</string>
    <string name="error_message_name">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="error_message_email">Enter Valid Email</string>
    <string name="error_message_age">Enter Age</string>
    <string name="error_message_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="success_message">Registration Successful</string>
    <string name="text_not_member">No account yet? Create one</string>
    <string name="text_already_member">Already a member? Login</string>
    <string name="error_email_exists">Email Already Exists</string>
    <string name="error_password_match">Password Does Not Matches</string>
    <string name="error_valid_email_password">Wrong Email or Password</string>
    <string name="text_member">Already a member? Login</string>
    <string name="error_email">Email Not Registered!</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="category_restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="category_trips">Trips</string>
    <string name="category_to_visit">Places To Visit</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close</string>

    <string name="geo_dei_frati">geo: 0,0?q= Dei Frati</string>
    <string name="geo_tratorian">geo: 0,0?q= Trattorian Artisan Food </string>
    <string name="geo_la_ceaun">geo: 0,0?q= La Ceaun</string>
    <string name="geo_tratoria_pocol">geo: 0,0?q= Trattoria Pocol</string>
    <string name="geo_sergiana">geo: 0,0?q= Sergiana, Muresenilor</string>
    <string name="geo_athanasios">geo: 0,0?q= Athanasios</string>
    <string name="geo_belvedere">geo: 0,0?q= Belvedere, Stejerisului 11 </string>
    <string name="geo_gott">geo: 0,0?q= Gott </string>
    <string name="geo_hopaa">geo: 0,0?q= Hopaa </string>
    <string name="geo_mamboa">geo: 0,0?q= Mamboa</string>
    <string name="geo_sub_tampa">geo: 0,0?q= Sub Tampa </string>


    <string name="Brasov">Beautiful Brasov</string>
    <string name="aboutTown">
        \t\t\tFringed by the peaks of the Southern Carpathian Mountains and resplendent with gothic,
        baroque and renaissance architecture, as well as a wealth of historical attractions,
        Brasov is one of the most visited places in Romania.\n
        \t\t\tThe entire territory of the county falls in the catchment area of Olt river,
        which crosses the county from the confluence with the Negru River to the confluence with Ucea river,
        over a distance of 210 km. The most important tributaries of the river Olt in the county are:
        Timis, Ghimbasel, Barsa, Homorodu Mare and Sercaia.\n
        \t\t\tBrasov county owns 32 protected areas and an impressive number of nature monuments.The county is home
        to the National Parks Piatra Craului (14,795 ha) and Bucegi (32,663 ha).
        The reserve in the Bucegi Mountains includes: Abruptul Bucsoiu, Malaesti, Gaura, where various
        fauna species are protected, such as chamois, lynx, mountain cock, as well as rare flora species.
        Piatra Craiului Mountains are completely protected, hosting about 40 percent of the endemic species in Romania,
        a representative example being the carnation of Piatra Craului, a unique species in the world. \n
        \t\t\tThe list of natural monuments includes: several fossiliferous places, The Basalt Columns at Racos, the
        Dopca Gorges, the Basalt Columns at Piatra Cioplita, the Basalt Micro-canyon at Hoghiz, the Basalt Rock at Rupea,
        the caves Barlogul Ursului and Valea Cetatii. The list of natural reserves includes: Harman Swamp, Tampa Mountain,
        Bogatii Forest, the Narcissus Glade at Dumbrava Vadului, Postavar Mountain, Dealul Cetatii - Lempes, Cotul Turzunului,
        Stejerisul Mare, the Forest and eutrophic swamps at Prejmer, the Geological Complex Racosul de Jos, Holbav, Comana Cave,
        Ciocas Hill - Vitelului Hill.\n
        \t\t\tForests account for over 35 percent of the entire area. The main natural resources of the county are:
        coal deposits - lignite (Vulcan), marble (Sinca Veche), limestone (Brasov, Brasov, Zarnesti and Racos),
        basalt and andesite (Racos and Bogatii Forest), sandstone (Teliu), thermal waters (Brasov) and iodo-sodium waters
        (Persani, Rotbav and Homorod), mineral waters (Zizin.
    </string>

    <string name="restaurant_image_description">restaurant image</string>
    <string name="restaurant_location_icon">restaurant location icon</string>
    <string name="restaurant_phone_icon">restaurant phone icon</string>

    <string name="trip_image_description">trip image</string>
    <string name="trip_location_icon">trip location icon</string>

    //info about what to do OUTSIDE in Brasov
    <string name="aventura_parc">Aventura Parc</string>
    <string name="bran">Bran Castle</string>
    <string name="cantacuzino">Cantacuzino Castle</string>
    <string name="dino">Dino Park</string>
    <string name="peles">Peles Castle</string>
    <string name="rasnov">Rasnov Citadel</string>
    <string name="zoo">The Zoo</string>
    <string name="bears">Bear Sanctuary</string>

    <string name="geo_aventura_parc">geo: 0,0?q= Aventura Parc</string>
    <string name="geo_castelul_bran">geo: 0,0?q= Castelul Bran</string>
    <string name="geo_castelul_cantacuzino">geo: 0,0?q= Castelul Cantacuzino</string>
    <string name="geo_dino_parc">geo: 0,0?q= Dino Park</string>
    <string name="geo_castelul_peles">geo: 0,0?q= Castelul Peles</string>
    <string name="geo_cetatea_rasnov">geo: 0,0?q= Cetatea Rasnov</string>
    <string name="geo_gradina_zoo">geo: 0,0?q= Gradina Zoologica</string>
    <string name="geo_sanctuarul_ursilor">geo: 0,0?q= Rezervatia de Ursi Zarnesti</string>

    //info about the sights to visit in Brasov
    <string name="biserica_neagra"> Black Church </string>
    <string name="geo_biserica_neagra">geo: 0,0?q= Biserica Neagra </string>
    <string name="biserica_neagra_d">
        \t\t\tThe Black Church is one of the most impressive religious edifices in Romania.
        Its construction began in the 14th century as a Roman Catholic structure and it was known as the Church of Saint Mary.
        It was built on the place of another older church. The first priest of this new church was a man named Thomas Sander.
        He died in 1410 and his grave can be found inside the church, in the choir area.\n
        \t\t\tCompleted by the end of the 15th century, the church belongs to the last stages of Gothic architecture.
        The result was a three-nave basilica, all the same height, as was preferred during the 15th and 16th
        centuries in the German lands, where most of the architects and masons originated.
        The Catholic services were replaced with Lutheran ones during the Protestant Reformation.\n
    </string>


    <string name="council_square"> Council Square </string>
    <string name="geo_piata_sfatului">geo: 0,0?q= Piata Sfatului </string>
    <string name="council_square_d">
        \t\t\tThe Council Square is the central starting point for most tourist attractions in Brasov such as the Black Church -
        the most famous in the city, built between 1377 and 1477, Republic Street and Muresenilor Street, Sforii Street,
        Ceara Gate and Ecaterina Gate, Altea Dupa walls with White Tower, Black Tower and Graft Bastion, Tampa Area,
        Unirii Square where St. Nicholas Church and Museum Complex \'Prima Prima Scoala Romana\' are located.
    </string>

    <string name="first_school"> First Romanian School </string>
    <string name="geo_prima_scoala">geo: 0,0?q= Prima Scoala Romaneasca </string>
    <string name="first_school_d">
       \t\t\tThis has been a centre for Romanian teaching and book printing for centuries.
        The small museum houses countless Romanian ‘firsts’: the oldest Romanian bible (printed on goats’ skin),
        oldest letter written in Romanian using the Latin alphabet (previously, Romanian was written with Cyrillic letters),
        a page from an 11th century schoolbook and much more.
        The printing press itself printed only 39 books, taking 20 workers and eight translators months to finish just one book.
        No wonder a book was worth 12 oxen in those days. Also here is the tiny Museum of the Junii (Muzeul Junilor),
        showing the seven different traditional costumes the Schei men wore; Schei women had only one.
    </string>

    <string name="st_nicholas"> Saint Nicholas Church </string>
    <string name="geo_biserica_sf_nicolae">geo: 0,0?q= Biserica Sfantul Nicolae </string>
    <string name="st_nicholas_d">
        \t\t\tThe building of the church in the Bolgárszeg suburb started in 1495 with the support of Vlad Călugăru,
        ruler of Muntenia. It was built on the place of an older church from 1292.
        The Orthodox Church and the adjecent school were the main intellectual and cultural support of the Romanians.
        It had an influence an all teritories inhabited by Romanians. Especially the work of deacon Coresi,
        who printed the first ecclesiastical books in Romanian.\n
        \t\t\tThe monarchs of the time also played a major role in adonrning and expanding the church,
        by offering money, gold and silver objects, ikons, and ceremonial objects.
        Even the Russian empress, Elisabeta Petrovna, donated to the church.
        The XVIII century restoration works highly affected the original Gothic look of the church giving a
        Baroque style to the building. The frescos made then are still preserved today.
        The church cemetery is the resting place of such well-known people as Dicolae Titulescu,
        the famous diplomat, dr. Aurel Popovici, the great politician of his time, Vasile Saftu, the poet, and many others.
    </string>

    <string name="turnul_alb">White Tower</string>
    <string name="geo_turnul_alb">geo: 0,0?q= Turnul Alb </string>
    <string name="turnul_alb_d">
        \t\t\tThe White Tower (Turnul Alb) is located directly above the Bastionul Graft,
        and you can climb up to it via some very steep steps – do not try it unless you are
        feeling extremely fit and agile. There are more steps when you actually get to the tower,
        but the views from the top are fantastic.
    </string>

    <string name="dupa_ziduri">"Behind the Walls" Alley</string>
    <string name="geo_dupa_ziduri">geo: 0,0?q= Strada Dupa Ziduri </string>
    <string name="dupa_ziduri_d">
        \t\t\t“După Ziduri” Alley, meaning “behind the walls”, is a narrow sidewalk between the northern
        defensive walls and a forest covered slope. At one end we find the Blacksmiths’ Bastion,
        currently the State Archives. Above the alley a path takes us up to the Black Tower (“Turnul Negru).
        Dating back from the 15th century, the tower got its name after being struck by lightning and turning black.
        To me, it looked rather gray… Behind it, we saw a couple of holes, clearly dug by human hands into the rock,
        probably some old tunnels that used to connect the towers to the city. If only we would have brought our
        flashlights along… Continuing along the path we reached the White Tower (“Turnul Alb”),
        which is a little bigger and got its name from the white paint that always covered it.
    </string>

    <string name="casa_muresenilor">Muresenilor House</string>
    <string name="geo_casa_muresenilor">geo: 0,0?q= Casa Muresenilor </string>
    <string name="casa_muresenilor_d">
        \t\t\tOn Piaţa Sfatului western side stands the intimate Mureşenilor House Memorial Museum,
        which honours the family of Jacob Mureşan, the first editor of the Romanian-language Gazeta de
        Transilvania, a political newspaper published in the 19th century.
    </string>

    <string name="brasov_citadel">Brasov Citadel</string>
    <string name="geo_cetatea_brasov">geo: 0,0?q= Cetatea Brasov </string>
    <string name="brasov_citadel_d" >
        \t\t\tThe place is one of the best points if you want to have an entire view over the city.
        From the top of the hill, two totally different panoramas can be seen:
        On one hand you can explore the "new city" or rather say the communist one in a bird s eye view…
        (Ah I forgot to tell, for some years during communism, the city of Brasov was named Stalin city. )\n
        and on the other side, you can admire the old city with the Black Church
        in the middle and the name of the city Brasov is written in a mountain face the same like Hollywood style.
    </string>

    <string name="weavers_bastion"> Weavers Bastion</string>
    <string name="geo_bastionul_tesatorilor">geo: 0,0?q= Bastionul Tesatorilor </string>
    <string name="weavers_bastion_d">
        \t\t\tThe bastion was built in two phases between 1421-1436 and 1570-1573.
        Part of it collapsed in 1701, thus it was reconstructed in 1750 and restored in 1910.
        The hexagon shaped building occupies 1.616 sq.metres and its thick (1.5-3m ) battered walls also have
        loopholes for pouring tar. On the ground floor there are crevices for cannons.
        On the interior side of the walls there are 3-4 storey hallways. In 1800 two other constructions
        were built for the guilt, while in 1807, when the bastion lost its protective function a watch house
        was built to the entrance. \n
        \t\t\tThe year 1908 brings along changes and the bastion becomes the scene of more and more cultural events.
        Due to its excellent acoustic even opera nights were held here. Since 1950 it houses a museum.
        The permanent exhibition entitled \'Brasov castle and the Bársza country fortresses\' displays
        weapons from the middle ages, products made by the guilds, the scale model of the city in the middle ages,
        made by Friedrich Herman in 1896, as well as the scale model of Schei.
    </string>

</resources>
